<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: vanet | DynaMid]]></title>
  <link href="http://dynamid.citi-lab.fr/news/categories/vanet/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://dynamid.citi-lab.fr/"/>
  <updated>2017-09-27T10:10:50+02:00</updated>
  <id>http://dynamid.citi-lab.fr/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Dynamid Team]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microscopic vehicular mobility trace of Europarc roundabout, Creteil, France]]></title>
    <link href="http://dynamid.citi-lab.fr/news/2015/05/06/microscopic-vehicular-mobility-trace/"/>
    <updated>2015-05-06T11:58:00+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://dynamid.citi-lab.fr/news/2015/05/06/microscopic-vehicular-mobility-trace</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="http://vehicular-mobility-trace.github.io/assets/img/header_bg.jpg" alt="Micromobility" /></p>

<p>Understanding the dynamics of vehicles is a major issue in smart cities
evolution. Most intelligent transportation systems concentrate on macro-
mobility with centralized decisions and global optimizations for whole
cities. With the great development of autonomous cars and vehicle-to-vehicule
communication systems, micro-mobility is again of special importance for
opportunistic data dissemination and local decisions - for instance when
arriving at traffic lights or when vehicles meet.</p>

<p>Simulation tools are widely used to evaluate assumption correctness and
performances of optimization algorithms. Several macroscopic vehicular
mobility trace exist, but few detailed ones at the microscopic level. Most of
macro traces integrate simplistic models for intersections and roundabout,
while the complexity of this fine-grained mobility can greatly affect the
global optimization. For that purpose, we propose a dataset describing a
complex roundabout in Creteil, France.</p>

<p>Feel free to play with it ! #OpenData #SmartCity</p>

<p>Available at <a href="">http://vehicular-mobility-trace.github.io</a></p>

<p>Great job by Marie-Ange who coordinates this #JointWork between INSA-Lyon,
VALEO Group and Val-de-Marne Region !</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
